<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="Welcome">Welcome To Wheaton Dining! </string>

    //Action Bar Button Names
    <string name="ChaseButtonName">Chase </string>

    <string name="EmersonButtonName">Emerson</string>

    <string name="DavisButtonName">Davis</string>

    <string name="BalfourButtonName">Balfour</string>

    //Dining Fragment Main Buttons

    <string name="LyonBucksButtonName">Lyon Bucks</string>

    <string name="DiningLocationsButtonName">Dining Locations</string>

    <string name="MealPlanButtonName">Meal Plans</string>


    //Misc

    <string name="MenuName">Menu</string>

    // meal plans

    <string name="Meal_Plans1">
        A Meal Plan unlocks delicious meals, coffee, snacks, and more,
        at 4 locations across campus. Your Meal Plan includes Meal Swipes and Lyons Bucks,
        conveniently loaded onto your Wheaton Student ID. No need to carry additional cards or cash!
    </string>

    <string name="MealPlanName">Meal Plans</string>

    <string name="LyonBucksTitle">Lyon Bucks</string>



    <string name="Meal_swipes1">As a residential college, Wheaton requires all students living on campus to enroll
        in one of the meal plan options available through the Colleges Dining Services.
        Each fall, all students are enrolled in the Carte Blanche Plan.
        Returning students only, have the option to change plans during the months of May and June when online enrollment
        is open or during the first two weeks of the fall semester.   </string>

    <string name="LB1">Lyons Bucks may be used at any Wheaton College Dining location.
        Visit the location page for location information,
        including dining hall menus and hours of operation.
        Unused Lyons Bucks roll over from fall to spring and expire at the end of the spring semester.  </string>

    <string name="LS1">You may also use a Lyons Swipe (Meal Exchange) for breakfast,
        lunch and dinner at Emerson, Hood, or Davis.
        The Lyons Swipe can be used for a specified meal at each location.  </string>






</resources>