<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="financial_name">Welcome to the Financial Aid Office</string>

    <string name="financial_description">A College education is one of the most important investments you will make. We hope the following information will provide you with the tools you need to formulate your college plans. Our office is located on the second floor of the Admission Building.\nPlease do not hesitate to contact us if you have any questions. We look forward to working with you!</string>

    <string name="financial_deadline_info">Wheaton administers over $50 million in funds through our academic scholarship, need-based financial aid, and alternative financing programs annually. In order to be considered for need-based funding it is important to meet your financial aid application deadline. Late applicants will be reviewed on a funds-available basis.</string>

    <string name="application_plan">Application Plan</string>
    <string name="fin_aid_deadlines">Financial Aid Deadlines</string>

    <string name="financial_first_years">Financial aid application deadlines for First-Year Applicants</string>
    <string name="regular_dec_spring">Regular Decision (spring entry)</string>
    <string name="regular_dec_spring_date">November 15</string>

    <string name="early_dec_1_spring">Early Decision 1</string>
    <string name="early_dec_1_spring_date">November 15</string>

    <string name="early_act_spring">Early Action</string>
    <string name="early_act_spring_date">November 15</string>

    <string name="early_dec_2_spring">Early Decision 2</string>
    <string name="early_dec_2_spring_date">January 15</string>

    <string name="regular_dec_fall">Regular Decision (fall entry)</string>
    <string name="regular_dec_fall_date">January 15</string>


    <string name="financial_transfers">Financial aid application deadlines for Transfer Applicants</string>
    <string name="transfer_spring">Transfer (spring entry)</string>
    <string name="transfer_spring_date">November 15</string>

    <string name="transfer_fall">Transfer (fall entry)</string>
    <string name="transfer_fall_date">May 1</string>


    <string name="financial_returning">Financial aid application deadlines for Returning Students</string>
    <string name="returning_students">Returning Students</string>
    <string name="returning_students_date">May 1</string>


    <string name="financial_final_info">These deadlines are required for consideration of need-based financial aid. Students who wish to be considered for academic scholarships only do not need to complete a financial aid application. Academic scholarships require no additional application; recipients are selected from the incoming freshmen applicant pool by the Office of Admission. Please Note:  Late credentials will be accepted and reviewed for funding as resources permit.
                                        \n\nFinancial aid applicants will no longer be required to complete a CSS Profile.  Students who wish to apply for all forms of financial assistance must complete 2021 – 2022 Free Application for Federal Student Aid (FAFSA) and the Wheaton Application for Financial Aid.
                                        \n\nFirst year applicants must upload documents through their admission application portal. Returning students should submit requested documents directly to the Office of Student Financial Services by email, fax, or U.S. Post.</string>

    <string name="financial_contact_info">For more information please contact us at: </string>
    <string name="financial_office_email">sfs@wheatoncollege.edu</string>

    <string name="financial_website_info">Or visit us in our <a href="https://wheatoncollege.edu/about-wheaton-college/offices-services/student-financial-services/">website</a>.\n</string>

</resources>